Life is uncertain and expected to be
sad, the
plan is fixed
on the future, the financial security which was lost and the
data should be required,
we do not know how to provide them
[Music] The
trend is to provide all the possible
smart
[Music] [Music] This option should be given to all [Music]
[Music]
This option Life Option Act Rewa The
correct answer of lakhs of watches Bheembhut
personality Daurita Gurutvashishta Lagoo
Pai middle cover Hui Thani
This Chaudhary related
[Music]
This plan is through a medium of a little one Get unlimited
term Kimba complete policy
on the premium Devra Naumania premium related
ICICI PR I Protect financial
need should be fulfilled by
giving permission to the following option Have kidnapping
hit officer Provide live cover
First voters hit Rasila who utare
all love Rasiya ko motor horoscope
[Music]
This is the chance to complete the plan
Sheikh and Gaurav
ICICI PR I Protect smart do
base life ka bhar and reached the
target Tankara Gurudutt and Asustata
Sahitya Bhartik 18
[Music]
Continued [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
[music]
[applause]